GREGORY MENO

phone 407 493 3734

location 29 Wiltshire dr. Avondale Estates, GA 30002

email greg.meno@gmail.com

online https://github.com/GregMeno

TECHNOLOGIES

HTTP, REST JSON, SQL python erlang go javascript c, c++

Celery, RabbitMQ memcached django, Flask

Solr, Haystack, Tastypie

IRC GTK, Qt

Postgres, SQLite

AWS

SOFTWARE

Linux, MacOS, plan9 git, svn

vim acme

xchat.

pyflakes, fugitive

dpkg, apt pdb, strace

jira, trac, Review Board

bash, sed

COMMUNITY

attended DjangoCon2013
attended ManagerTools EMC/ECC
member PyATL
member CLUG
member StackOverflow
attended pyCon2011
attended pyCon2010

EDUCATION

University of Central Florida, Orlando BS, Computer Science 2005

PROFILE

My python knowledge is strong and I can learn new technology with speed and ease. My professional experience covers eight years programming in Unix-like environments. I have worked as an individual, part of a team, and as a manager. From this experience I am confident that I can work effectively with all types of people.

EXPERIENCE

Manager, Software Development, CMG Technology Atlanta, GA 6/2012 - Present

I manage a team of seven developers. My responsibility includes delivering projects relating to the core platform and revenue optimization. This year I lead an integration with Google's DFP API which saved the RevOpt department a hundred man-hours in migration effort. I organized the Cox Media Group presence at DjangoCon this year which included; making a recommendation on how many employees to send, budgeting and forecasting the cost, led creative ad creation, and representing my company in the community.

Software Developer, CMGd Atlanta, GA

6/2010 - 6/2012

I helped build a massive Django CMS called Medley which serves 6M request/day. I maintained an ubuntu virtualbox image and setup scripts containing all that is necessary to start contributing to our CMS in an hour or less. Over the course of a year I presented four lunch and learns on a variety of technical topics. I co-taught a six session class for all members of our team on proper unit-testing. I mentored a developer who is new to the software industry. My advice on matters relating to python, Linux, and git are highly sought after. Recently I have lead an effort to improve and simplify the ad management system that enables our advertising team to generate a large portion of our revenue.

Software Engineer, IDEAL Technology Orlando, FL

10/2005 - 6/2010

I worked on development, operations, and testing on STRIKETM a digital media exploitation device. We delivered this system in six months. My influence brought functional specification to our development cycle. I have leveraged open source libraries to create custom filesystem drivers in userspace. My pyGTK code allows users to customize the way STRIKE extracts data, analyzes data, and display data intuitively. I designed and wrote a process that is used to provide in-field updates to our customers. In this position Also, I mentored junior developers by giving talks, reviewing their code, providing constructive feedback, and sizing tasks appropriately.

Programmer, International Aviation Advisors Orlando, FL

4/2003 - 12/2004

I maintained and modified an online value forecast simulation written in c and Perl. My duties included code verification, web application development, and scripting tests.

Jr. Systems Administrator, Quasar.net Orlando, FL

1/2002 - 2/2003

I managed and maintained debian based Linux web servers. I wrote scripts in Perl to facilitate bandwidth reporting.